## Ms. Tống Nhật Chân

MEDICAL COMMUNICATION SPECIALIST



■ tongnhatchan@gmail.com 
 0915687561 
 Mekong Delta, VietNam

## **OBJECTIVE**

Devoting individual pratical experience, perceived knowlegde, gained skills to the overall success of the organization.

Being keen on finding a challengeing position within an ambitious company where I will be able to continue to accumulate more experience and lead to personal fulfilment.

Making commitment to work with: loyalty, the learning willingness, responsibility, high concentration on accomplishing the work target.

### **EDUCATION**

## Võ Trường Toản University

October 2011 - March 2016

## Major: Pharmacy

GPA: 3.6/4

### WORK EXPERIENCE

**Fuji Medic Limited Liability** Company in Can Tho -**Providing the periodical** health examination service.

October 2016 - June 2018

### Sales - Interpreter - Administration

- Sales: Searching potential customers, contacting and liasing with them resulting in: Introducing the company service, dealing price, analysing the customer's demand and the service capacity to come up with the win-win deals.
- Interpreter: Supporting foreigner supervisor connect to departments of company, customers as well;
- Administration: Preparing all official letters and exchanging with Governmental Departments and customers; Organizing all internal meeting and internal documents; Contacting to part-time doctors for organizing health-check plans, proceeding the payment. Preparing labour contract for whole personnel. Keep on track with the compliance with internal regulation and labour law among staffs.

## **Hello Health Group**

July 2016 - August 2017

## Medical Editor

- Based on the weekly content from superior, extending the content by collecting or analysing knowledge form science sources such as Science-Direct, Webmd, CDC etc.

## Traditional Medicine Can Tho Hospital

September 2015 -October 2015

### Intership

- -Working as a pharmacist at the Pharmacy Department of the Hospital.
- -Preparing medicinal herbs to patients in/out the hospital based on the prescription.

## **ACTIVITIES**

# The 10th Việt Nam – France Cooperation Conference

14th September 2016 - 17th September 2016

# Volunteer at Rạch Súc Church.

June 2016 - July 2016

## Social Network Club of Võ Trường Toản university

2015 - 2016

#### **Translation club**

2015 - now

## Speaking up 2012 contest

March 2012

#### Volunteer

- -The conference was held in Can Tho. Its aim is to exchange information about health, social, culture between two countries.
- -My responsibilities: Transfering all information between guests and the organizer, guiding the guests how to join the conference

## English Teacher

- -The church offers free course to poor children, which is organized every summer holidays in Can Tho.
- -My responsibilities: preparing the outline of grade 8 English; lecturer on the class; translator for foreigner volunteers.

#### Collaborator

- Following activities at my university: student camping, singing constests, students clubs, ....to collect news for online articles. It aims to introduce my university images to social network like Facebook.

### Translator

- -The club belongs to The Bridge Of Clinical Pharmacy Group which is organized by Pharmacists from over the nation.
- -My responsibilities: translating news or scientific articles in the field of Clinical Pharmacy.

## Candidate

- A competition which is held by American Embassy for students from Mekong delta region.
- The aim of the contest is to understand how the young people think about their future: what they love to do, what challenge they have to face etc. also share how they are energetic.

## **CERTIFICATION**

IELTS Certificate with Band 6 on Nov 2016

TOEIC Certificate with score 845 on Jan 2016

Informatics Certificate with Good score in 2015

### **SKILLS**

Analytical and
Strategic thinking
Relationship building
and net-working
Business planning
Communication